副總統剛剛走進司法部大樓
The Vice President just entered the Department of Justice.
現場請到的是艾拉·薩伊德
We're here with Ayla Sayyad,
她發表在《華爾街電訊報》上的文章
whose Wall Street Telegraph article
直接促成了這次調查  艾拉
catalyzed the investigation. Ayla.
關鍵問題在於白宮與此事是否有牽連
The issue at stake is whether the White House was in any way involved.
是否有國外資金用於換取政治支持
Was foreign money traded for political favors?
又是否對外交關係產生影響
Did it influence diplomatic relations?
單是為來自中國的政治獻金洗白就是違法的
Just the act of laundering Chinese contributions is illegal.
如果這筆錢對白宮決策產生影響的話
If it had a significant impact on White House policy,
那就是更嚴重的罪行了
that's a far more serious crime.
你曾多次與丹尼爾·拉尼根會面
You've met with Daniel Lanagin on multiple occasions.
沒錯  2003年起我們曾11次共處一室
We were in the same room, yes, on 11 occasions since 2003.
但其中我們交談過的只有三次
But we only spoke on three of those occasions.
那幾次已經標出來了
Those instances are highlighted.
你們談了什麼
What did you discuss?
那都是在籌款會上
Well, these were fundraisers.
我對著幾十號人發表講話
I speak to dozens of people,
也沒有什麼特定的話題
usually about nothing at all.
我是南方人  鄧巴女士
I'm southern, Ms. Dunbar.
我媽媽教導我
My mother taught me that
席間講話不僅禮貌
conversation during mealtime is not only polite,
還有助消化
it aids the digestive process.
那你沒有跟他談到過
So you didn't speak to him
阿道希部落向這些超級政治行動委員會捐款的事嗎
about the Adohi tribe's contributions to any of these super PACs?
絕對沒有
Absolutely not.
我從不和支持者提超級政治行動委員會
I never discuss super PACs with any supporters.
我們熟悉法律規定
We both know the law.
在這些禮節性的談話中
During one of these polite conversations,
拉尼根先生可曾向你提起過馮山德
do you recall Mr. Lanagin ever mentioning Xander Feng?
我想沒有
I do not.
你聽說過這個名字嗎
Does that name mean anything to you?
你是說除了鋪天蓋地的媒體報道嗎
Other than being plastered all over the news?
從這個角度說  就像我也聽說過金·卡戴珊
In that regard it means as much as Kim Kardashian.
那我再說得明確些
Then let me be more specific.
你對馮先生的政治活動有什麼瞭解
What knowledge do you have of Mr. Feng's political activities?
這是你丈夫的意思還是
Is this coming from your husband, or is it...?
是我的意思
From me.
而且不是說我不再支持法案了
And it's not that I don't support the bill anymore.
只是採訪的事
It's just the article.
我們已經答應讓馬特做專訪了
We've promised Matt an interview.
那往後推幾周吧
Maybe in a few weeks,
等調查塵埃落定之後再說
once the investigation has died down.
《紐約時代雜誌》可不會乾等著我們
The New York Times isn't going to wait for us.
他們已經騰出十月份的封面
They've already scheduled the cover for October.
鑒於我們的安排
Based on our timing --
那就恕難參與了
Then I can't be a part of it.
是因為嘉樂威的事  是不是
It's the Galloway nonsense, isn't it?
克萊爾  別這麼說
Claire, come on.
沒事的
It's okay.
你直說就行  我們是朋友
You can say so. We're friends.
的確影響不好
It doesn't help.
你不會真相信我
You don't actually believe I --
當然不信
No.
但國內還是有不少人信的
But enough of the country still does.
加勒特現在需要爭取每一份支持
And Garrett needs every bit of support he can get right now.
那你心意已決了
So there's no convincing you?
我會盡可能幫你
I'll help as much as I can.
悄悄地幫
Quietly.
有傳言說你和馮先生
There are rumors that you and Mr. Feng
在去年五月的貿易峰會上進行了私下接觸
served as back channels to the trade summit last May.
沒錯  就是"傳言"
Exactly. Rumors.
峰會期間馮就在美國境內
We have Feng in the U.S. during the summit.
就算他做了私下接觸
Well, if he was back-channeling,
就算我知情
and even if I were aware,
這種外交接觸一般都是保密的
any form of diplomatic communication is usually classified.
你和總統說起過馮嗎
Have you ever discussed Feng with the President?
北京每一個權勢人物我們都會說起
Any major player in Beijing is worthy of discussion.
那就是承認了
So that's a yes.
只是陳述一般情況
It's a general comment.
你在能源危機期間與別人說起過他嗎
Did you discuss him during the energy crisis?
我猜你是指跟他合資投資精煉廠的
I assuming you're alluding to the refinery co-venture with --
沒錯  我是指雷蒙德·塔斯克
Yes. With Raymond Tusk.
我們從來沒聊起過精煉廠
The refinery was never part of our conversation.
我們要的是能立即見效的方案
We needed an immediate solution.
建精煉廠在短期內什麼都解決不了
A refinery would have solved nothing in the short term.
而且據我所知  這交易最後黃了
And it's my understanding that deal fell through.
沒錯  但塔斯克拿到了補貼
Correct. But Tusk did receive a subsidy.
其他核電供應商也都拿到了
As did every other nuclear energy provider.
但他和馮有聯繫
But his connection with Feng,
還有釤補貼
then a subsidy on samarium --
沒人從這筆補貼中獲利
Nobody made any profits off these subsidies.
至多也就是保本而已
At best they were breaking even.
事實上  雷蒙德一開始還反對補貼的事
In fact, Raymond fought us on the issue.
那我們再說說傑斐遜港大橋吧
Then let's back up to the Port Jefferson Bridge.
翻譯  章魚X
翻譯  冬麟
翻譯  香茗小焙
翻譯  某豚
翻譯  艾瑞卡
翻譯  衛老哥
翻譯  癢癢
翻譯  澤川
時間軸  chance-coco
後期  餓得慌
特效  寶寶
顧問  老杜
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第二季  第十一集
人人影視傾情奉獻
這也怨不得她  這的確值得擔憂
I don't blame her. It's a valid concern.
告訴他我不會談嘉樂威的事
Tell him I won't engage on Galloway,
所以乾脆也別問
so there's no point in asking.
這可是馬特·貝
This is Matt Bai.
他要問什麼我們說了不算  而他肯定會問這個
We can't dictate what he'll ask. And he will ask.
那我就說我不會回應這些無聊八卦
Well, then I'll just say I won't answer tabloid questions.
這是個合理的問題
It's a legitimate question.
醜聞對選舉有什麼影響
How the scandal could affect the vote.
我建議我們也不做了
Look, I say you pull out, too.
取消掉整篇專題
We scrap the whole piece.
傑姬在和我們對著干
Jackie is fighting us.
總統方面又指望不上
The leadership is noncommittal.
我們需要這篇專訪讓大家重新關注法案
We need this article to refocus attention.
但這於你不利啊
But it'll hurt you.
對你的形象和法案都不利
Both your personal image and the bill.
但如果我們誰都不靠
But if we cut the cord,
約好的兩場採訪
we schedule two interviews,
就這麼取消了  馬特不會生氣嗎
then we cancel, won't Matt be furious?
那麼大家只會看到我們的退縮
The story will be about pulling out.
我們要權衡利弊
We're talking about the lesser of two evils.
我不希望你成為目標
I don't want you to become the target,
-使我們的努力白費  -如果不是我去呢
- to undo all the work - Then what if it's not me at all?
可你說第一夫人不打算
But you said the first lady wasn't going --
不是她  是其他人
Not her. Someone else.
建設大橋是否是換取切斷共和黨資助金的籌碼
Was the bridge a trade-off to prevent additional GOP funding?
據我所知
As far as I know,
這座大橋是總統在兌現
the bridge was a delivery on a promise
他對選民做出的承諾
the president had made to the voters.
還沒問完嗎
Are we finished here?
快了
Almost.
你會見過多少位國會議員  鄧巴女士
How many members of Congress have you interviewed, Ms. Dunbar?
200嗎
About 200?
194位
194.
我想幫忙
Well, I want to be of help,
但我想前面194位都已經說得差不多了
but I doubt I can offer any more than the 194 that preceded me.
我得到了一些有用的證詞
I have gotten some useful testimony.
-從誰那兒  -眾議院高層
- From who? - A high-ranking House member.
領導層的嗎
In the leadership?
我不能說
I'm not at liberty to say.
鮑勃·博奇  傑姬·夏普
Bob Birch? Jackie Sharp?
這個人說他參加了7月14日
This individual says he attended a meeting
在總統辦公室的會議
July 14th in the Oval Office.
她說是個男的  那麼一定是博奇
She said "He," so it must have been Birch.
雷蒙德肯定能輕易收買他
I'm sure Raymond had no trouble buying him off.
你也參加了那次會議
You attended that meeting also.
看來是這樣的
It appears so.
你還記得那次會議的主題嗎
Do you recall the subject of that meeting?
一波共和黨的攻擊廣告
A wave of conservative attack ads.
我們沒有足夠財力與之抗衡
We were being outspent.
你一定很震驚吧
It must have been quite a shock
拉尼根轉而把錢捐給了另一黨派
when Lanagin's tribe shifted contributions to the other party,
之前他們從沒給共和黨捐過錢
when they hadn't given a single dime to the Republicans before that.
這的確會令我們震驚
Well, it would have been a shock,
但我們當時並不知道錢是哪來的
but we didn't know where the money was coming from at the time.
據我的線人說
According to my source...
鮑勃·博奇
Bob Birch.
我的線人說  當時預計有兩千五百萬
My source says the estimate was 25 million.
引用你說的話
You said, and I quote,
"憑空出現這麼多錢
"With this kind of influx,
肯定有人違規了"
you can be sure somebody isn't playing by the rules."
像是我說過的話
Sounds like something I might say.
鮑勃的記性比我好
Bob has a better memory than me.
傑斐遜港大橋剛獲批
The money stopped just after
這筆錢就中斷了
the Port Jefferson Bridge was approved.
你是真有想法
Is there a theory here,
還是查不出頭緒就瞎猜
or are you just grasping at straws?
大橋與馮有關
The bridge leads to Feng.
馮與拉尼根和塔斯克有關
Feng gives me Lanagin and Tusk.
塔斯克和總統
Tusk and the president --
鄧巴女士  你想玩六度分隔的話
Ms. Dunbar, you want to play six degrees of separation,
還能扯上吉米·霍法和教皇
you could throw in Jimmy Hoffa and the pope.
82年神秘失蹤的工會領袖
那麼一度分隔如何
Then how about one degree of separation?
道格拉斯·斯坦普  你的幕僚長
Douglas Stamper, your chief of staff.
這是7月14日他在拉尼根的賭場
This is him at Lanagin's casino July 14th.
我用這些申請了搜查證  調出了飛行記錄
I used these to get a warrant for flight records.
第二天  斯坦普先生飛去北京
The next day, Mr. Stamper was on a flight to Beijing.
他為什麼去賭場
Why was he at the casino?
為什麼去北京
And why was he in Beijing?
我想與委託人談談
I would like to speak to my client.
請吧
Please.
我很努力
I work hard.
我不拖泥帶水  我知道重要的是什麼
I keep things simple. I know what my priorities are.
但是有這麼個人
But there's this -- this person.
她不在我的生活中  而是在我生活的邊緣
She's not even in my life, except on the edges,
所以界限很模糊
making things blurrier.
這並不讓我想喝酒
It doesn't tempt me to drink.
那感覺更像...
It's more like she --
她給我的感覺就像我喝酒時的感覺
it's more like she feels what it was like when I was drinking.
總是無法滿足
When I couldn't get enough.
不管我喝多少酒
No matter how many drinks I had,
總是喝不夠
I wanted another.
我不想和她在一起
I -- I don't want to be with her.
我是說  我想
I mean, I -- I -- I do.
但是
But
她更像是我女兒
it's more like she's my daughter.
或者我母親
Or my mother.
我也不知道了  太亂了
I don't know. This is fucked up.
慢慢說
Take your time.
我不該再跟她聯繫了
I should cut her off.
就像戒酒一樣
The way I did with booze.
就這些  說完了
That's all. I'm done.
謝謝你與我們分享
Thanks for sharing.
我們需要一些時間回答你的問題
We'll need some time before responding to your questions.
我願意等
I could wait as long as necessary.
可能要花上一段時間
It could take a while.
事關國家安全
There are national security matters at stake.
副總統需要咨詢顧問
The vice president needs to consult with his advisors.
國家安全
National security?
你真要用這招嗎  奧利弗
Are you really gonna play that card, Oliver?
他的回答可能涉及保密信息
His answers could entail classified material.
我們什麼時候能得到回應
When can we expect a response?
我會通知你的
I'll let you know.
我們可以拿走這些截屏照片嗎
May we hold onto the screen cap?
請便
Be my guest.
我們會盡快聯繫你  鄧巴女士
We'll be in touch soon, Ms. Dunbar.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President?
不要認為你這就沒事了
If you think you're insulated, don't.
我們調查的不止道格拉斯·斯坦普
Our investigation is much bigger than Douglas Stamper.
就到這兒吧  鄧巴女士
That's enough, Ms. Dunbar.
多謝你的配合  副總統先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Vice President.
樂意合作
Happy to cooperate.
剛出虎口  又入狼窩
From the lion's den to a pack of wolves.
如果你是滴血的肉  那就殺了別人
When you're fresh meat, kill,
給他們更新鮮的肉
and throw them something fresher.
你好  我是菲茨
Hey, I'm Fitz.
道格
Doug.
你要知道  你可以自己硬挺著
Yeah, you know, uh, you can isolate,
獨自承擔這一切
white-knuckle this shit if you want.
或者你也可以向他人求助
Or you can ask for help.
你有擔保人嗎
Got a sponsor?
不用  都已經14年了  我沒事
No. It's been 14 years. I'm good.
電話在背面  如果你改主意的話
Number's on the back, if you change your mind.
我以為你有司機
Thought you had a driver.
我有
I do.
我不希望他聽到什麼
I didn't want him overhearing anything.
你根本就不該來這個州
You shouldn't even be near this state.
我不在這兒
I'm not really here.
去加州繞了點遠路
Long layover on my way to California.
稽核員
I've got auditors,
和聯邦探員都在我辦公室
federal agents in my office,
查看每一份文件和檔案
going through every file, every document.
他們連我的垃圾都翻
They're going through my god damn trash.
如果她傳喚你就堅持保持沉默
Just stick to the Fifth if she subpoenas you.
他們怎麼知道去查斯坦普
Well, how do they know to look for Stamper?
專查那天的錄像
To search the tapes on that exact day?
別亂下結論
Don't jump to conclusions.
你這是要犧牲我
You're throwing me under the bus.
安德伍德才是對頭  你不是
Underwood's the roadkill. Not you.
他們要坑我
They're going to fuck me.
他們會找到辦法
They'll find a way.
-而且你也知情  -如果是那樣
- And you know that. - And if that's the case,
你和你的家人會得到妥善安置
you and your family will be taken care of.
他們已經給我提供認罪條件了
They're already offering me a plea.
你還沒被起訴呢
You haven't even been charged yet.
如果我合作的話
If I cooperate.
你能少坐幾年牢
You'll do less time,
但你的家人會一無所有
but your family will have nothing.
等你出來他們還是一無所有
They'll still have nothing when you get out.
你作證指認雷蒙德
You testify against Raymond,
他也不會有事  因為他們只有你的證詞作證據
and he'll still walk because all they'll have is your word.
而現在你的證詞沒多少可信度
And that doesn't count for much right now.
他要是不害怕你就不會來了
You wouldn't be here if he wasn't afraid.
我來不是因為他害怕了
I'm not here because he's afraid.
是因為你害怕了
I'm here because you are.
我要確定你不會做蠢事
And I want to make sure you don't do anything stupid.
在反覆和北京溝通後
After repeated conversations with Beijing
他們堅持他們的立場
they remain intractable in their position.
我今早命令一個航母戰鬥群
This morning I gave orders for a carrier group
在沖繩海域重新部署
to reposition near Okinawa.
這樣我們的艦隻不會直接
This won't put our ships in direct confrontation
和中國軍艦對峙
with the Chinese vessels,
但又能把對方納入航母空襲範圍
but it will put them within reach of airstrikes.
我今天晚些時候會知會中國大使
I'll be informing the Chinese ambassador later today.
我們會和五角大樓聯合發表聲明
We'll release a statement in coordination with the Pentagon.
先生  我們的釤儲量
Sir, our stockpiles of samarium
最多能再堅持兩個月
will only last another two months at most.
如果我們這麼做
If we go this route --
我已經知道所有人的擔憂
Yeah, I've -- I've heard everyone's concerns.
這是我的決定
And this is the decision I've made.
有問題嗎
Any questions?
好的  謝謝
Okay. Thank you.
弗蘭克
Frank.
進行的怎麼樣
How'd it go?
我們有些問題需要後續澄清
We have a few follow-up questions that we have to address.
比如什麼
Like what?
沒什麼要緊的
Oh, nothing major.
就是零七碎八  一點細節
Just odds and ends. A few details.
我以為這調查會簡短而溫和
I was under the impression this would be short and sweet.
我也以為  但她不依不饒
So was I, but she's very deliberate.
這事得盡快平息  弗蘭克
We need this over, Frank.
至少要盡快撇清跟白宮的關係
At least as far as the White House is concerned.
我們不能分心
We can't be distracted.
特別是局勢如此緊張的時候
Not with warships on the move.
我確信馬上就會結束了
I'm confident we're in the home stretch.
你看上去不像嘴上說得那麼輕鬆
Well, you seem more concerned than you're letting on.
不  完全沒有
Oh, no, not at all.
你在搓手
You're fidgeting.
是我的畢業戒指
It's my class ring.
我忘了我...
I forget I --
我把它埋了
I buried it.
什麼
You what?
說來話長了
I -- it's a long story.
我從沒見過你這麼緊張  弗蘭克
I've never seen you this stressed before, Frank.
我從沒見過您這麼疲憊  先生
Well, I've never seen you this tired before, sir.
您也有自己的圈
You've got rings of your own.
黑眼圈
Dark ones.
越發明顯了  是嗎
Yeah, they're getting worse, aren't they?
您該在總統辦公室的沙發上多打打盹
You should take more naps on those sofas in the Oval.
如今光打盹可管不了用了  弗蘭克
Oh, naps don't cut it these days, Frank.
一點都解不了乏
Not even a dent.
謊話連篇
Lie after lie.
先是對檢察官  現在是對總統
First to a prosecutor, then to a president.
我覺得我全無防護
I feel exposed.
就像我手指上曾被戒指庇護的皮膚
Like the skin where my ring used to be.
強如阿喀琉斯  也終因踵上一箭斃命
Even Achilles was only as strong as his heel.
道格在哪  他老不接電話
Where's Doug? He's not answering his phone.
他去參加互助會了  先生
He went to a meeting, sir.
大白天的去幹什麼
In the middle of the day?
他現在可能在往回趕了
I think he's on his way back now.
我要他趕緊回來
I want him back now as soon as possible.
先生  這是給你的
Sir, this arrived for you.
是雷米跳槽去格蘭頓-希爾時你送給他的手錶
The watch you gave Remy when he left for Glendon Hill.
我從手錶背面的名言認出來的
I recognized it from the quote on the back.
他留信息了嗎
Was there a message?
沒有  只有這塊表
No. Just the watch.
趕緊聯繫道格
Let's find Doug.
好的  先生
Right away, sir.
希望你不介意塑料杯子
Forgive the plastic.
呂克·圖伊曼斯  他有真本事
Luc Tuymans. He's the real thing.
那我就信你了
Well, I'll take your word.
這不是我的  這些全都不是
It's not mine. None of it.
在加州  你要是想賣房子
California, you want to sell your house,
你的房屋中介會先裝修一番
your realtor decorates it.
起碼會裝個樣板間
Well, one room at least.
你打算搬到哪去
Where you moving?
我在索諾瑪有座小農場
Oh, I have a little ranch in Sonoma.
我妻子離開了
My wife's gone.
我的孩子也不和我說話
My kids won't talk to me.
至少我還有我的畫
But at least I'll have my painting.
你還畫畫嗎
You paint?
不畫  農場也是胡扯
No. And there's no ranch.
但其餘的話  其餘的都是真的
But the rest of it -- the rest of it's true.
乾杯
Cheers.
我是為傑奎琳·夏普而來
I'm here about Jacqueline Sharp.
我們在考慮僱用她
We're thinking of hiring her.
做說客嗎
A lobbyist?
她可能贏不了連任競選了
She could lose her re-elect.
現在局勢對在位者不利
Not a great time to be an incumbent.
我知道你和她關係很近
I know you two are close.
你來是想要什麼
So, you're looking for what?
推薦函嗎
A recommendation?
我們是K街員工流動率最低的一家
We have the lowest turnover of any shop on K Street.
K街上有很多智囊公司  遊說公司和倡導團體
這是有原因的
There's a reason.
格蘭頓-希爾想用什麼樣的人
What are you looking for at Glendon Hill?
心狠手辣的人
A killer instinct.
那你找她算是找對人了
Well, she certainly has that.
恕我直言
Forgive me if I'm prying,
但是不是她造成了你的...
but did she have anything to do with your, uh...
出局
Departure?
傑姬做了她必須做的事
Jackie did what she had to do.
我永遠不會原諒她
I'll never forgive her.
但我理解她為什麼要這麼做
But I understand why she did it.
她究竟做了什麼
Did what exactly?
我用現金買的票
I paid cash for my ticket.
我非常謹慎
I was careful.
顯然不夠謹慎
Clearly not enough.
先生  賭場裏到處是攝像頭
Sir, the casino had cameras everywhere.
我根本無法避開
There was no way to avoid them.
但他們的監控錄像肯定有幾千小時
But there had to have been thousands of hours of footage.
他們怎麼找出來的...
Now how they found that --
有個問題我必須要問  道格
I have to ask you a question, Doug.
我很抱歉  但你要如實作答
And I'm sorry, but I need you to be honest.
你是不是又開始酗酒了
Are you drinking again?
當然沒有
God no.
真的嗎
Truly?
想都沒想過
It's not an option.
你最近的表現可很像喝醉了
Because it would explain a lot.
你完全有權生氣
You have every right to be upset.
-這是我的錯  -我已經顧不上生氣了
- This was my fault. - I'm more concerned than I'm upset.
我現在需要你  道格
I need you now, Doug.
非常需要
More than ever.
我明白
I know.
你我都不年輕了
We're not young men.
一旦失敗  都會老死在牢裏
If we fail, we'll die in a cage.
我最近不在狀態
I haven't been myself lately.
你14年前也是這麼說的
That's what you said to me 14 years ago.
我給了你第二次機會  也收穫了回報
When I gave you a second chance, it paid off.
你戒酒了  道格
You got clean, Doug.
這份工作是我最看重的  先生  無比重要
Nothing means more to me than this job, sir. Nothing.
無論發生了什麼
Whatever's going on,
我要知道你能搞定
I need to know that it can be managed.
如果你需要我的幫助
And if you need my help,
我會伸出援手
I'm here to help you.
我沒事  先生
I'm good, sir.
我能解決好  局面會好轉的
I can handle myself. Things'll be different.
我從沒給過別人第三次機會
I've never given someone a third chance.
但現在我再給你一次機會
Until this very moment.
我非常感激
And I'm grateful.
我不會讓你後悔的
You won't regret it.
請相信這一點  先生
Please believe that, sir.
是雷米讓他們找到錄像的
It was Remy who alerted them to the footage.
這是他的離職禮物
His going-away gift.
讀讀背面
Read the back.
你覺得他想傳達什麼信息
What do you think he's trying to say?
我不知道  找到他  給我安排一次會面
I don't know, but track him down and set up a meeting.
鄧巴那邊怎麼辦
What about Dunbar?
我們沒法逃開事實
We can't run from the facts.
你讓我說什麼  我就說什麼
I'll say whatever you want me to say.
我負全責
I'll take responsibility for all of it.
她可能會起訴你
She could indict you.
幕僚就是做這個的
That's what having a staff is for.
我有個更好的解決辦法
I have a better solution.
-我們一起承擔責任  -怎麼做
- We'll both take responsibility. - How?
後天和鄧巴安排一次會面
Set up an interview with Dunbar. Day after tomorrow.
-我們倆需要時間做足準備  -是  先生
- You and I need time to do our homework. - Yes, sir.
這是什麼時候弄的
When did this happen?
密查姆幫我修好了
Meechum helped me fix it.
如果他們不讓我跑步  我總得想辦法健身
If they're not gonna let me run, I have to work out some way.
你把它搬上樓了
You carried it all the way up here?
更隱秘  有人幫我
For privacy. I had help.
-密查姆  -沒錯
- Meechum. - That's right.
他還真是樣樣通
Well, he's a jack of all trades.
-工匠  搬傢俱的  -肉盾
- Handyman. Furniture mover. - Human shield.
有多糟
How bad is it?
很糟
Bad.
他們有證據證明道格出現在不該出現的地方
They have evidence of Doug being where he shouldn't have been.
你打算怎麼辦
What are you gonna do?
講實話
Tell the truth.
-你該不會真打算...  -不是全部
- You're not actually gonna -- - Selectively.
別擔心
Don't worry.
不過絆了一下  還沒摔倒
It's a stumble, not a fall.
如果只是絆一下  你不會這個樣子
You aren't like this when it's just a stumble.
-什麼樣子  -你害怕了  我看得出來
- Like how? - You're scared. I can tell.
1分39秒劃五百米  這是我的最佳成績
500 meters at 1:39. That was my best.
以此為目標吧
Shoot for that.
墮胎等於謀殺
墮胎傷害女性
丟   人
通 奸 者
你怎麼樣
How have you been?
挺好
Okay.
-藥挺有用的  -那就好
- The meds are helping. - Oh, that's good to hear.
坐吧
Let's have a seat.
街角那些人
Those people at the end of the street...
鬧得挺厲害
it's intense.
他們一天到晚不消停  週末人數還翻番
They're there 24/7. Twice as many on the weekends.
我們現在都習慣了
We're so used to it by now.
我能脫鞋嗎
Can I take off my shoes?
我覺得該穿得正式點  但我真不喜歡高跟鞋
I thought I should dress up, but I am not good with heels.
行  當然可以
Yes. Of course.
我媽媽說和裙子很搭
My mom said they went with the dress.
舒服多了
Much better.
梅根
Look, Megan,
我知道過去六個月很難熬
I know the last six months have been difficult,
但我需要你的幫助
but I need your help.
我們沒能像預想的那樣得到領導層的支持
We just don't have the support that we expected in the leadership.
我也猜到你不會只是想問問我的近況
Yeah, I figured this wasn't just about checking up on me.
你之前改過主意  我理解
You changed your mind before, and I understand why.
但現在你的情況似乎穩定多了
But now it seems as though things are more stable with you.
你願意嗎
Are you willing?
我都坐在你家了  說不有點過意不去
It's hard to say no when I'm in your house.
你也聽到了外頭那些人
Well, you hear those people out there.
他們聲音很響  但我們要發出更高的聲音
They're loud, but I think we need to be louder.
但這聲音不能是我的
And it can't be my voice,
因為我已經是嬰兒殺手  和出軌者
because I'm the baby killer, the cheater.
這聲音得是你發出的
It needs to be your voice.
因為你沒有污點
A clear voice.
我已經在軍事法庭上作證了
I'm already testifying at the court martial.
但那裏不對媒體開放
But that's closed to the media.
還不夠
It's not enough.
這種事曾發生在很多人身上
There are so many people this has happened to.
為什麼一定是我
Why does it have to be me?
因為是你打來了電話
Because you're the one who called.
你打算在麥金尼斯判刑之前發表嗎
Are you gonna try to put it out before McGinnis gets sentenced?
賽斯  有空嗎
Seth? You have a minute?
馬特  我一會兒打給你
Matt, I have to call you back.
關門
Close the door.
副總統錄用你的時候
When the vice president brought you on board,
我是反對的
I advised against it.
但我不得不承認你幹得很好
But I can't deny you've done a good job.
謝謝你這麼說
I appreciate you saying that.
我一直很注重保護副總統
I'm very protective of the vice president.
我很難跟旁人分擔這份職責
I find it hard to share that duty with anyone else,
這也導致我可能出錯
which leaves me open to error.
這是我的缺點之一
It's one of my faults.
正如我跟副總統說的那樣
As I told the vice president,
我知道信任需要我自己爭取
I understand that trust is something that I need to earn.
而且我得到工作的途徑不正
And given how I got the job --
如果副總統信任你  那我就信任你
If the vice president trusts you, then I trust you.
我們現在是一個團隊
We're a team now.
而且我也沒法孤軍奮戰
And the truth is I can't do this alone.
要我做任何事都行
Anything and everything you ask of me.
可能與媒體無關
It might have nothing to do with the media.
新聞發言人不過是個名號
Press Secretary is just a title.
很好
Good.
我們有兩個任務
We have two tasks.
首先  找到雷米·丹頓
First, find me Remy Danton.
但要小心
But be discreet.
我去找他
I'll track him down.
其次  我要你翻閱副總統的行程記錄
Second, I need you to go through the Vice President's travel logs.
過去十年的所有記錄
Everything in the past 10 years.
我們要找什麼
What are we looking for?
任何軟肋
Anything that could hurt us.
我從前往後找
I'll work forward.
你從後往前
You work backward.
馬上去辦  還有道格
I'm on it. And Doug?
謝謝
Thanks.
刪除瑞秋?
刪除
南茜  幫我訂部新手機
Nancy, I need you to order me a new phone.
追蹤
道格拉斯·斯坦普
刪除聯繫人瑞秋
手機追蹤
中斷
你說是"零七碎八""馬上就會結束"
You said "Odds and ends." The "Home stretch."
我幾個小時前才看到了這些內容
I was presented with this information just hours ago.
這是能招致彈劾的罪行  弗蘭克
We're talking about impeachable offenses, Frank.
完全不會  先生
Not at all, sir.
你的幕僚長...
Your Chief of Staff was --
我當時覺得賭場跟這事有關
I had a gut feeling that the casino was involved.
我派道格去查了
I sent Doug down there to get to the bottom of it.
你一發現聯繫就該馬上去找司法部
You should have taken this to the DOJ the first inkling you had --
我當時就不想那麼做
That's exactly what I didn't want.
萬一沒有什麼  我卻製造事端
To create some ruckus if nothing was going on?
你不能私自調查  弗蘭克
You can't go on conducting your own investigations, Frank.
查明真相  盡職調查  隨您怎麼說
Fact-finding, due diligence, whatever you want to call it.
如果有任何違法行為  我必須知道
If any laws were being broken, I wanted to know.
你就要這麼跟鄧巴說嗎
And that's what you want to tell Dunbar.
我不想透露我們的外交手段
That I didn't want to disclose our diplomatic protocols.
我擔心中期選舉
That I was concerned about the midterms.
我還想保護美國總統
And that I wanted to protect the President of the United States.
或許我做得不對
Now, maybe what I did was wrong,
但我沒幹任何違法的事
but I didn't do anything illegal.
你確定
You certain of that?
我跟我的律師認真探討過了
I've discussed this at length with my lawyers.
即使我們承認這一切
Dunbar does not strike me as the sort of person
我覺得鄧巴也不會就此打住
who will put on the brakes, even if we admit all of this.
反而還可能促使她繼續深挖
In fact, it might encourage her to dig deeper.
說得對
You're right.
所以我打算上交我全部的行程記錄
Which is why I want to hand over all of my travel logs.
我覺得您也該這麼做
And I think you should, too.
自願上交嗎
Volunteer them?
是的  表示我們樂意合作
Yeah. As a gesture of cooperation.
我們表示做得夠多了
Haven't we made enough gestures?
這樣她就不會那麼叫勁了
That'll take the wind outta her sails.
不  我不想讓她
No. I don't, uh, want her,
仔細查看我所有的行蹤
uh, poring over every one of my comings and goings.
他是在擔心他的婚姻咨詢
He's worried about his marriage counseling,
他也該擔心
as he should be.
如果您是在擔心您的婚姻咨詢
If you're worried about your marriage counseling,
您不必擔心
you shouldn't be.
如果被外界知道  會造成多大影響
Imagine the fallout if the public were to find out that --
那是大海裏的一根針
A needle in a haystack,
還不是鄧巴要找的那根
and not a needle that Dunbar is looking for.
她已經會見了一半的國會議員
She's interviewed half of Congress.
這女人是要見血
That woman's after blood.
而不是八卦
But not for gossip.
就算她真的起疑了
And even if she does raise an eyebrow,
您只是去探望一位生病的朋友  不是嗎
you were visiting a sick friend, weren't you?
是的  表面上是這樣
Yeah, ostensibly.
這她沒什麼可說的
Well, she couldn't possibly find any fault with that.
叫嘉利克過來
I'd like Galich in here.
那我就不打擾了
I'll let you two talk privately.
你什麼時候去見鄧巴
When are you seeing Dunbar?
明天  這樣您也有時間準備
Tomorrow, so you have some time.
我會跟比爾談談  回頭找你
Well, I'll speak to Bill and get back to you.
他會建議您不要這麼做  這是他職責所在
He'll advise you against it, which is his job.
但我會強烈建議您想想政治而不是法律
But I would just encourage you to think politics and not legalese.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
議員女士
Congresswoman?
我為什麼要投票給你
Why should I vote for you?
沒事  馬克
It's -- it's okay, Mark.
晚安
Goodnight.
你看起來很疲憊
You look tired.
忙了一天競選嗎
Long day on the campaign trail?
你在這幹什麼
What are you doing here?
你沒跟我說過哈維梅耶女兒的事
You never told me about Havemeyer's daughter.
大家都知道
Everyone knows that.
全世界都知道
The whole world knows.
但不知道你常去探望她
But not that you visited her.
而且是你洩露出去的
That you leaked it.
你大老遠跑來加州就是為了問我這些
You came all the way to California to ask me about that?
我是到了加州才知道的
I came to California to find out about that.
我提出買下哈維梅耶的房子
I offered to buy Havemeyer's house,
但他就那麼告訴我了
but he told me for nothing.
你說得對
You were right.
我確實忙了一天競選
It has been a long day on the trail.
現在還不相上下
It's still a close race.
要是選民知道你是怎麼當上黨鞭就不會了
But not if the voters know how you became whip.
你這是在威脅我嗎
Are you honestly threatening me?
安排和弗蘭克的會面
Set up a meeting with Frank.
我不在乎你怎麼說
I don't care what you talk about,
只要是你單獨一人  會面也有記錄就行
long as you're alone and the meeting is on the books.
然後你去和鄧巴談
Then you're gonna sit down with Dunbar.
她已經問完我了
I've already done my interview.
告訴她  是弗蘭克逼你那麼說的
Tell her Frank grilled you on your testimony.
作偽證嗎
Perjure myself?
保住你的位子
Save your seat.
你說出去吧
You know what? Tell everyone.
想想那會有什麼後果
Think how that'd play out.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你真要為了弗蘭克毀了自己嗎
You'd really toss yourself off a cliff for Frank?
我不效忠於弗蘭克·安德伍德
I have zero allegiance for Frank Underwood.
我不會受他操縱
I won't be manipulated by him.
我更不會被你操縱
And I sure as fuck won't be manipulated by you.
我不是虛張聲勢
I'm not bluffing.
那我就是對的
Then I was right.
關於什麼
About what?
你根本不在乎我
How little I meant.
那跟這個沒關係
That has nothing to do with this.
當然有關係
It has everything to do with this.
我應該覺得噁心  但我沒有
I should feel disgusted, but I don't.
只是特別失望
Just supremely disappointed.
我們十分鐘前接到電話
We got the call 10 minutes ago.
直接從白宮顧問那裏打來的
Direct from the White House counsel.
總統要上交一切嗎
The President's turning over everything?
從他就職那天開始
From the day he took office.
肯定會包括他去拜訪那位朋友嗎
And we're sure this includes the visits to his friend?
當然  安保人員全部出動
It has to. It was full security detail.
老天啊
Phenomenal.
我們有下手的地方了
We have something we can work with.
關於我的記錄...
Now, as for my logs...
沒有問題
They're clean.
你拿生命打包票嗎
You'd bet your life on that?
是的
I would.
我也是  先生
Me, too, sir.
我們已經檢查了兩次  反覆檢查
We've been through 'em twice, backward and forward.
我的聲明呢
My statement?
在你的收件箱裏
In your inbox.
我看過了  塞斯幹得很漂亮
I looked it over. Seth did a nice job.
會面一結束我們就要把消息發佈出去
We need to go wide with this the moment the interview's over,
這樣鄧巴如果打算發佈什麼消息
so that we beat Dunbar to the punch
我們可以先發制人
in case she decides to release something.
我會守在電腦前
I'll be at my computer,
一收到道格的消息就按下"發送"鍵
ready to press "Send" the moment I hear from Doug.
你們倆睡過覺嗎
Have either of you slept?
我們很清醒  全速運轉
We're awake. Fully operational.
你去洗個澡  換件衣服
You take a shower and put on a fresh suit.
是  先生  我們在那邊見
Yes, sir. I'll see you over there.
你有至少三小時
You have at least three hours.
打個盹吧  去我辦公室睡
Take a nap. You can use my office.
你作證的時候麥金尼斯將軍就在法庭裏
General McGinnis was in the courtroom when you testified.
是的
Yes.
你私下見過他嗎
Had you seen him in person --
在他侵犯你之後
I mean, since he assaulted you?
沒有
No.
那是什麼感覺
So what was that like?
不愉快
Not fun.
怎麼個不愉快
Not fun how?
很難受  真的很難受
It was hard. Really hard.
聽著  梅根
Look, Megan,
我同意把文章的焦點轉移到你身上
I -- I agreed to change the focus of my piece to focus on you,
我也知道這肯定很難
and, you know, I know this has gotta be hard.
但你得幫幫我
I need you to help me out a little bit.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是很擅長這個  我很緊張
I'm not very good at this. I'm nervous.
你打電話去安德伍德夫人的訪談時挺好的
You seemed fine when you called into Mrs. Underwood's interview.
她在電話那頭跟我在一起
She was there with me on the phone.
你的緊張情緒
Your nerves.
我知道自你被侵犯後  這一直是個問題
I know that's been an issue since the assault.
那種防禦心理
The defense brought up
引起了情緒與精神的不穩定
what they called emotional and mental instability.
總是那樣
That's what always happens.
被攻擊的人會再次被攻擊
The person who was attacked gets attacked all over again.
你有什麼感覺
How did that make you feel?
讓我覺得憤怒
It made me angry.
律師一直問我恐慌癥的事
The lawyer kept coming after me about my panic attacks,
和我的抗抑鬱藥
my antidepressants.
但我只是緊緊盯著麥金尼斯
But I just kept staring at McGinnis.
我想讓他知道我能承受
I wanted him to see I could take it.
我很堅強
That I was strong.
我想讓他先轉過臉去
I wanted to make him look away first.
他有嗎
And did he?
是的  當我說到他不只是侵犯了我的身體
Yes. When I said he did more than violate my body.
還背叛了自己的國家
He betrayed his country.
毀了海軍陸戰隊的聲譽
He robbed it of a good Marine.
我們談談國會正在談論的
Let's talk about the Sexual Assault Bill
性侵法案吧
that's in front of Congress right now.
有人提出了很強烈的反對意見
You know it's taken some significant opposition,
尤其是另一個老兵
most notably from another veteran,
傑奎琳·夏普
Jacqueline Sharp.
要我說  她也背叛了自己的國家
If you ask me, she's betraying her country, too.
鄧巴女士
Ms. Dunbar.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
謝謝你多給我們幾天時間
Thank you for giving us a few extra days.
耐心對我來說不是問題
I have no problem being patient,
只要能因此得到坦率的回答
as long as it leads to forthright answers.
我不會讓你繼續等待了
Well, I won't make you wait a moment longer.
可以開始了嗎
Shall we?
你找到這裏了
Oh, you found it.
請坐
Have a seat.
我們馬上就完事了
We're just finishing up here.
你覺得怎麼樣  塔斯克先生
What do you think, Mr. Tusk?
留著還是剃了
Keep growing it or have it shaved?
還是留著吧
Ah, I guess I'll keep growing it.
沒問題
Ah, no problem.
我把後面清理一下
Let me just clean up the back here.
不了  麥克  讓我們單獨待會兒
No, Mack, if you'd give me a couple of minutes.
謝了
Appreciate it.
大概十年前我在這裏建造了這個地方
I had this place built down here about 10 years ago.
我厭倦了每兩周都要開車穿過整個城市
I got tired of driving all the way across town every two weeks.
現在坐個電梯就到了
Now it's just an elevator ride.
真方便
Convenient.
你知道不方便的是什麼嗎
You know what isn't convenient?
在我辦公室裏擠下八個律師
Cramming eight attorneys into my office.
那裏不是為召集我律所所有合夥人準備的
It was not designed for the entire partnership of my law firm.
他們比較擔心拉尼根
They're worried about Lanagin.
他有點害怕  但他能挺住
He's a little shaky, but he'll hold up.
安德伍德
Underwood?
博奇出手了
Birch delivered.
鄧巴提出斯坦普的問題了吧
And did Dunbar bring up Stamper?
會面是閉門的
The sessions are closed-door,
不過我想她肯定會提的
but I can't imagine she didn't.
那可憐的哈維梅耶那邊呢
And what about poor Havemeyer?
他在傑姬·夏普的事上對我們有幫助嗎
Was he any help to us on Jackie Sharp?
你的猶豫說明進展不順吧
I do not take your hesitation as a promising sign.
我向來不喜歡讓你失望
I never like disappointing you.
他什麼都不知道嗎
He had nothing.
不知道
No.
你覺得他是確實不知道呢
Now, do you think that's because there's nothing here,
還是他在保護她呢
or because he's protecting her.
他就是不知道
There's nothing there.
我可以再找一個別的議員
I can go to another congressman --
不行
No, no, no.
必須是個曝光率高的人
It has to be somebody high-profile,
領導層的人  才能引起轟動
someone in the leadership who will make waves.
那我再找找博奇
Let me get back to Birch.
太明顯了
Too obvious,
既然他擺明了不會對弗蘭克手軟
now that he's shown no sympathy for Frank.
算盤不能打得太響
This can't look orchestrated.
多線作戰  雷米
Multiple fronts, Remy.
必須得是傑姬·夏普
Has to be Jackie Sharp.
麥克
Mack?
把頭髮弄完吧
Let's finish up here.
我得回去幹活兒了
I gotta get back to work.
沒問題  老闆
You got it, boss.
你也得去幹活兒了
You need to get back to work, too.
我們說的事
And what we discussed?
把它們辦成
Make it happen.
你之前否認你是去私下接觸的人
You denied being a back channel.
我沒否認
I did not deny.
我沒有證實  因為這是機密信息
I chose not to confirm because it was classified.
但是你的辦公室一直否認
But your office has consistently denied --
我讓道格那麼做的
I instructed Doug to do so,
還有我的新聞部
along with my communications department.
私下接觸如果公之於眾
When a back channel becomes public,
也就沒什麼用了
it defeats its purpose.
精心編造的謊言
An orchestrated deception --
如果我們不予置評
If we had refused to comment,
人們就會知道確有其事
it would have suggested that it was true,
就會危及這一渠道
which would have endangered the process.
我實在沒辦法
I really had no choice.
馮先生目前在迪拜
Mr. Feng is currently in Dubai.
我知道
I know.
他因腐敗指控畏罪潛逃
He's fleeing corruption charges.
這不是他第一次被指控了
Not the first time he's been accused.
你的問題是什麼呢
And your question?
我知道是他洗錢  副總統先生
I know he laundered the money, Mr. Vice President.
我找到確鑿證據
It's just a matter of time
只是遲早的事
before I have the proof to substantiate that.
而我的問題就是  我再問一遍
So my question, which I am asking again,
你當時是否知情
is whether you knew.
那我就再回答一遍
And I will repeat my answer.
我當時並不知情
I did not.
我當時的確覺得有點不對勁
I did sense that something was awry,
道格知道我的擔憂
and Doug was aware of my concerns.
我覺得調查清楚是我的責任
And I took it upon myself to find out.
副總統並不知情
The vice president didn't know.
你不知道他去賭場的事嗎
You had no knowledge he was going to the casino?
不知道  但這並不代表
None. But that doesn't mean
我不對我手下的行為負責
I don't take full responsibility for my staff's behavior.
我責無旁貸
The buck stops with me.
那你發現了什麼
And what did you find?
什麼都沒發現  沒有非法行為
Nothing. No illegal activity.
我不像你那麼神通廣大
I don't have the same resources that you do.
如果你有所懷疑
If you suspected,
為什麼不立即聯絡國家印第安人博彩委員會
why didn't you go immediately to the NIGC,
印第安人事務局  或者...
the BIA, the Department --
你得理解
You have to understand.
我們中期選舉很吃力
We're facing very difficult midterms.
我不想為一些
I didn't want to bring attention
沒有實據的判斷而引發關注
to a series of allegations that may have no basis in fact.
或許這邏輯不是很合理
Now, that may have been misguided logic,
但這是我當時的選擇
but that's how I chose to act.
錯誤全在我一個人頭上
The mistake is mine and mine alone.
跟道格沒關係
Not Doug's.
當然更算不到總統頭上
And certainly not the president's.
我要是說我覺得
It shouldn't surprise you
我沒看到事情的全部  你不會意外吧
if I say it feels like I am not getting the full picture.
所以我打算把全部展示給你
Which is why I'm prepared to give you the full picture.
奧利弗
Oliver?
白宮相信透明度
The White House believes in transparency.
副總統全部個人出行記錄
All of the vice president's personal travel logs.
還包括我十年黨鞭任期內的記錄
And the last 10 years since I became whip.
和總統就職後的所有記錄
As well as the president's since inauguration.
我們會面的對象和時間都沒有任何問題
There should be no doubt as to whom we met with and when.
我很懷疑裏面的內容
I am skeptical about what this contains.
這點我們也預料到了
Which is what we anticipated
所以奧利弗會全程在場
and why Oliver will walk you through anything
陪你審查全部材料
you might need to know.
全都在那兒了
It's all there.
但如果你還有其他疑問或要求
But if you have any questions or requests,
我們也願意傾力協助
we'll be happy to facilitate.
剛開始我很緊張
I mean, at first I was really nervous.
但我一進入狀態
But then as soon as I started getting into it,
開始吐露心聲
starting speaking from my heart,
一切都自然脫口而出
all these things poured out.
那些我一度想說的
Everything I wanted to say.
我一直想說的都說出來了
That I've been wanting to say.
賽斯告訴我馬特很滿意
Seth told me that Matt was very impressed.
我還想做更多
I want to do more.
做更多採訪
More interviews?
報刊採訪  上電視
Articles. TV.
不論什麼都可以
Whatever it takes.
我想幫忙
I want to help.
這很好  梅根
That's great, Megan.
謝謝你給我這個機會
Thank you for making me do this.
這對我來說是邁了一大步
It was a big step for me.
你還要趕飛機
You have a plane to catch.
如果你需要我做別的採訪  我可以留下
I can stay longer, if you need me to do another.
不如你先回芝加哥
Why don't you head back to Chicago,
等我們制定好計劃
and as soon as we put a plan together
再給你打電話
we can give you a buzz?
我能喝杯水嗎
Can I get a glass of water?
自來水  還是瓶裝的
Tap is fine, or you want bottled --
我自己來
I can get it.
漢納希女士的車準備好了  夫人
We've got Ms. Hennessey's car ready, ma'am.
艾德華
Edward?
你去機場接她時
Did she seem all right
她看起來還好嗎
when you picked her up from the airport?
您的意思是
How do you mean?
我不確定  正常嗎
I don't know. Normal.
是的  可以這麼說
Yes. I'd say so.
她情緒起伏很大
She's very up and down.
反覆無常  容易激動
Very skittish and manic.
她確實有點緊張
I guess she did seem nervous.
我們沒怎麼交流
We didn't talk much.
我去看看她
I'll get her.
我在外面等
I'll be outside.
梅根
Megan?
我自己來
I've got it.
真的
Really.
我沒事
I'm okay.
車在外面等著了
The car is ready whenever you are.
謝謝你
Thank you for everything.
一路順風  保持聯繫
Have a safe flight. I'll be in touch.
我與鄧巴女士的談話卓有成效
I just had a very productive interview with Ms. Dunbar.
發新聞稿
Send out the press release.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
您還好嗎  夫人
You okay, ma'am?
我沒事  我只是打碎了
Oh, I'm fine. I just dropped...
請讓我來
Please, let me.
沒關係  我可以的
Oh, uh, it's fine. I'm fine.
不  我來  您光著腳
No, I've got it. You're barefoot.
艾德華  真的  沒事的
Edward, you don't have to. Really.
天啊  怎麼了
Oh, no. What happened?
該死
Damn it.
我去找繃帶
Let me get some bandages.
不用了
You don't have to.
我堅持  別動
No, I want to. Stay here.
目前的報導都是正面的
The coverage has been mostly positive so far.
鄧巴那邊呢
Dunbar's office?
他們只說很期待對記錄的審核
All they've said is they look forward to reviewing the logs.
有人提到道格嗎
Any heat on Doug?
有一些
Some.
很多人要求我發表評論
I'm getting a lot of requests for comments.
那是我的個人行動
I acted on my own.
我會全力配合司法部
And I will fully cooperate with the Justice Department.
可以這麼對外說嗎
We can put that out?
先生
Sir?
這或許會吸引更多注意
It might generate more interest.
注意我  而不是副總統
On me. Not the vice president.
無論什麼情況我都能應付好
I can handle whatever comes my way.
就這麼說
Put it out.
我去把最新的剪報都打出來  先生
I'll print you out the most recent clips, too, sir.
要想辦法向鄧巴透露風聲嗎
Should I find a way to tip off Dunbar?
還是順其自然吧
Let nature take its course.
我們剛找到雷米
We got a hold of Remy.
他剛回來了
He just got back to town.
他在哪
Where is he?
我跟你的安保隊都安排好了
I've arranged everything with your detail.
你做得很好  道格
You've done good work, Doug.
謝謝你  先生
Thank you, sir.
菲茨
好了  這樣好多了
There. That's much better.
謝謝  夫人
Thanks, ma'am.
我得走了
I'm gonna get going.
抱歉我有點喝醉了
I'm sorry I'm a little drunk.
這裏是您家  您可以隨心所欲
It's your house. You do whatever you want.
你也該喝一杯酒
You should have a glass of wine.
謝謝  夫人  但是...
I appreciate that, ma'am, but --
你已經下班了  對嗎
You're off your shift, right?
是的  沒錯
I am. That's true.
那就不許說不喝
Then I won't take no for an answer.
您不該把好東西浪費在我身上
Uh, you shouldn't waste any of your good stuff on me.
我其實根本不懂品酒
I don't really know anything about wine.
那喝點波本威士忌怎麼樣
Then how about bourbon?
你肯定想喝一點
I bet you like a little of that.
我當然不介意能喝點波本威士忌
I definitely don't mind a bourbon from time to time.
那就喝波本威士忌
Then bourbon it is.
你現在很難找啊
You're a tough man to track down these days.
你拿到手錶了
You got the watch.
變則善
"To improve is to change."
常變則至善
"To perfect is to change often."
那你想要什麼樣的變化呢
What sort of change are you looking for?
讓我有選擇餘地的變化
Whichever leaves me options.
在格蘭頓-希爾遇到麻煩了
Trouble at Glendon Hill?
帶薪休假  直到調查結束
Paid leave till the investigation is over.
至少是帶薪的
Well, at least you're being paid.
這是終止我合夥人身份的第一步
First step in terminating my partnership.
這種事你也懂
You know how things go.
無論發生什麼
No matter what happens,
這都是我洗不掉的污點
there's a stain I can't wash out.
那麼你在尋找就業機會嘍
So you're looking for career opportunities.
我並不是要把自己整個賣給你
I'm not offering myself to you wholesale.
我會繼續跟你鬥  但是力度會小一點
I keep fighting you, but I can fight you less.
你說"小一點"的意思是...
And by "less" you mean...
讓你痛  但不會讓你完蛋
Enough to hurt, but not finish you.
作為回報  我在格蘭頓-希爾之外也有前途
And in return I have a future beyond Glendon Hill,
不管是什麼樣的前途
whatever that might look like.
那麼你是要保持中立
So you offer neutrality,
但最終會追隨勝利者
but you'll go with the victor.
我想看著更厲害的人獲勝
I figure let the best man win.
如果你失敗了
And if you go down,
不會是因為我
it won't be because of me.
這已經挺夠意思了
That's worth something.
你這是為什麼
Where is this coming from?
保險  沒別的
Insurance. That's all.
這跟傑姬有關嗎
Does it have anything to do with Jackie?
已經結束了
That's over.
我知道你已經收服了博奇
I know you've got Birch in your pocket.
你不會選擇烏麥克  我們太親密了
Womack's not an option. We're too close.
但是傑奎琳
But Jacqueline...
這單純是關於我的前途
This is about my future, pure and simple.
跟她沒關係
She's not a part of it.
留著這塊表吧  就當做誠意的象徵
Keep the watch, as a token of good faith.
他雖然否認  但他在保護她
He might deny it, but he's protecting her.
他沒有意識到的是
What he doesn't realize is
我比雷蒙德更不在乎傑姬
I have even less regard for Jackie than Raymond does.
可憐的雷米
Poor Remy.
感情用事
The heart can choke the mind
理智就會受到影響
when all its blood flows back unto itself.
他說"我不喜歡深色頭髮的女孩"
He said, "I don't like brunettes."
看來我差點錯過了派對
Looks like I almost missed the party.
我已經下班了  先生
I'm off the clock, sir.
別緊張  弗蘭西斯  我打破了一個杯子
Oh, relax. Francis, I broke a glass,
艾德華被一塊碎片割傷了手
and Edward cut his hand on a piece of it.
天吶
Jesus.
我得給你換繃帶了
I have to change that.
把那個解下來  我去拿新的...
Take that off, and I'll get fresh...
我希望您不要介意  先生
I hope you don't mind, sir.
我下了班...
I was off-duty --
她是不是...
Is she, uh...
喝醉了嗎  有一點
Drunk? A little.
你喝了多少這東西
How many of these have you had?
喝了一點
A few.
不止一點吧
More than a few.
我可以用你的杯子嗎
May I?
用吧
Please.
讓我看看
Let me see.
沒什麼事
Oh, it's not too bad.
流了很多血
There's a lot of blood.
沒有看上去那麼糟
Looks worse than it is.
痛嗎
Is it painful?
喝了酒不那麼痛了
The bourbon helps.
如果痛你就說
Now you let me know if this hurts.
一點都不痛  先生
Not one bit, sir.
你頭痛嗎
How's your head?
沒事
Fine.
睡前吃了幾片阿司匹林
Took a few aspirin before I went to sleep.
你呢
You?
我睡得可香了
I slept like a baby.
很好  你需要好好睡一覺
Good. You needed that.
怎麼了
What is it?
很奇怪
Something weird.
有個地址老是出現
This one address keeps popping up.
安德伍德嗎
Underwood?
總統
The president.
早上好  密查姆
Morning, Meechum.
早上好  副總統先生
Morning, Mr. Vice President.
真是美好的一天
It's a beautiful day.
當美國政府爆出醜聞  需要進行徹底調查時
為了避免司法部的調查偏向現政府
國會會要求司法部任命特別檢察官  進行全權獨立的調查
特別檢察官的人選必須是不擔任政府公職的人員
美國歷史上最著名的特別檢察官
當屬哈佛大學法學教授阿奇伯德·考克斯
1973年5月  考克斯被任命為負責調查水門事件的特別檢察官
在調查過程中發現總統尼克松有違法嫌疑
尼克松遂命令司法部長解除考克斯的職務
但是當時連續兩名司法部長都拒絕了總統的要求
並辭職抗議  考克斯最終還是被尼克松政府解職
但是他仍然被認為在水門事件中發揮了非常重要的影響
克林頓擔任總統期間  在白水事件和萊溫斯基醜聞爆發後
肯·斯塔爾被任命為特別檢察官  調查克林頓一系列的醜聞
在他的努力下  國會啟動了對克林頓的彈劾程序
但是最終因為沒有獲得足夠票數  彈劾沒有成功
斯塔爾在克林頓醜聞期間也成為全美知名的政治人物
美國法律規定  只有公民才能在政治活動或選舉中進行捐贈
持有綠卡者也可以參加政治選舉活動進行助選
但除此之外  外國公民  包括在美國持有合法簽證者
都不能進行政治捐贈
最高法院對超級政治行動委員會做出裁定後
由於一些對超級政治行動委員會的捐款難以確定來源
一些政治組織也不對外公佈捐助者的身份
所以在2012年美國總統大選中  很多媒體質疑
會不會有外國政治獻金通過超級政治行動委員會
對特定候選人進行捐款  但是目前看  在大型的選舉中
尚沒有發現有確定的大額外國捐款者
本劇中的情節在現實中出現的可能性不大
2012年1月  美國最高法院在一項判決中
重新確認了不允許外國資金資助選舉的禁令